database = [
    {
        question: 'What is 14250 in scientific notation?',
        optionA: '1.425 x 10000',
        optionB: '1.43 x 10000',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Convert the following to decimal form: 3.233 x 10',
        optionA: '323.3',
        optionB: '32.33',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 0.000523123 in scientific notation?',
        optionA: '5.23123 x 0.0001',
        optionB: '5.23123 x 10',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10% of 120?',
        optionA: '15',
        optionB: '12',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8% of 80?',
        optionA: '6.4',
        optionB: '8.1',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: '15x - (-8x) is equal to?',
        optionA: '7x',
        optionB: '23x',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: '2 − 3x > 4 can be simplified to?',
        optionA: 'x > ⅔',
        optionB: 'x < -⅔',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: '2x(1 - 4) - 3x(3 - 2x) can be simplified to?',
        optionA: '-9x',
        optionB: '8 - 17x',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 12% of 12?',
        optionA: '1.2',
        optionB: '1.44',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Is y = 2x + 8.3 a straight line?',
        optionA: 'True',
        optionB: 'False',
        answer: 'A'
    }
]